♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we’ve got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright
on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we’ll
withstand it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there
when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we
will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko
stronger after all ♪
Now, then, if you provoke
a collision between two neutrons,
what do you obtain?
Who would like to answer?
Anybody?
Nobody?
Me, mam.
(CELL PHONES RING)
-Hello?
Hello?
Who is this?
Sissi, you, the principal’s daughter,
should know the rule
dealing with cell phones.
Now, why don’t you
remind us all what that rule is?
All mobile phones have got to be
turned off before entering the classroom
under penalty of having them confiscated.
Hand it over!
And that goes for everyone!
(STUDENTS CLAMORING)
Quiet down!
Put all your cell phones
on my desk right now!
XANA’s sure gonna be happy about this.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
We had this weird problem.
This morning, like everyone’s
cell phone started ringing and--
The teacher confiscated them. Us, too.
Crazy, huh?
All those calls
and no one at the other end.
I think I’ll contact Aelita.
This could be XANA’s doing.
We’ve got to do something.
If Jeremie’s right and we can’t
stay in contact, we’re in a real jam.
Hey, you three!
I’m organizing a meeting.
They’ve got to
give us our mobiles back.
Well, are you with us?
You bet we are.
Huh, no kidding?
If you really mean it,
we’ll see you in the
auditorium right after lunch.
You were right.
We’ve got to see what’s up.
Connection.
Aelita, do you read me?
Aelita?
Oh, hello, Jeremie.
Hi.
Tell me, have you noticed
anything strange on Lyoko?
No, should I have?
I don’t know, but I’d better
launch a scan to check.
Okay, and I’ll see if I can
pick up any of XANA’s pulsations.
Good, but be careful.
See you later.
You’re gonna take back your cell phone?
That’s called stealing, you know that?
No it’s not! Taking back what
belongs to you in the first place
is not what I would call stealing.
The students were warned.
I’m not going to return
their phones that quickly.
We need to deactivate
the school’s antenna.
That way, even with new phones
they won’t be able to use them.
Can you handle that, Jim?
Huh?
We have no choice, Yumi.
Thank you, Charles.
Okay, Ulrich. Let’s go.
The coast is clear.
Here we go.
Now, let’s see.
Oh, hello, Mister Lebrun!
Oh, hello, Ulrich.
Ha-ha! Mission accomplished!
Let’s hope that nobody finds out.
I’d rather hope that
we’re worried over nothing.
For now, the scan
hasn’t found an activated tower.
I haven’t seen anything either.
False alarm.
XANA!
Why would XANA be interested
in mobile phones, huh?
That’s what I’m hoping to find out
by checking out the school’s antenna.
I’m off to the meeting I promised Sissi.
Huh?
Hey, who let you guys up here?
Trying to stop me from
disconnecting the antenna?
Us? No, uh, we were just passing by.
Careful!
We’ll take him to the infirmary.
Okay.
I’ll try to find out what
XANA’s done to the antenna.
Hey, Jim, can you hear me?
It smells like roast chicken, huh?
Jim? Hey, Jim!
Yoo-hoo!
Odd? Ulrich?
What are you doing here?
Jim!
What happened to him?
Oh, you know how Jim is.
He’s a regular live wire, so--
Oh, I mean…
The main television antenna?
There.
Oh, Miss Yumi is gracing us
with her presence.
Where were you when we wrote the petition?
Just what is going on in here?
Oh, dad--uh, I mean…
Sir! What is going on here is this!
You see, we all signed a petition,
so you have to give us
back our cell phones.
Oh, really?
First, let me remind you
that in this establishment,
the students do not make the rules.
Secondly, Misses Hertz has just learned
that someone forced her locker open
to get back his cell phone.
It’s only normal, sir!
How can anyone live
without their cell phone?
I’m sorry, but this theft is another
reason for not returning them to you.
And we’re going to investigate to determine
who had the nerve to steal back his own.
And I say we don’t set foot
in the classroom without our mobiles!
(CHEERING)
You see these waves?
XANA’s using the school antenna unit
to try to plug into the main television dish.
That’s why all the phones rang?
Right. It jams their frequencies.
If XANA manages to take control of the dish,
he’ll have direct access to the satellites
that are now orbiting the earth.
And?
And he’ll be able
to guide a military satellite.
Okay, but for what reason?
I wish I knew. In peacetime,
these satellites are used for spying,
but if XANA reprograms one, who knows.
Anything can happen.
Jeremie’s right, this is serious.
You’d better believe it, Ulrich.
The scan has detected a tower!
Jeremie, XANA has activated
a tower in the polar region!
We’re on our way.
Better hurry.
Let’s go through the tunnel in the park.
Kiwi, you stay here.
No more phones, no more school! Perfect!
I’ll stay here in case XANA’s
got plans to attack the school.
Hey, are you with us or not?
Ever heard of solidarity?
Don’t worry, Sissi,
I’m with you 100 percent.
No more phones, no more school!
No more phones--
Okay, let’s go!
Kiwi, what are you doing here?
Incredible. For a dog,
he’s stubborn as a mule.
Well, now that you’re here, come on.
Yeah!
Aelita’s on her way to the polar region.
Aelita?
Jeremie, I made it to the ice flow,
but I don’t see any activated tower.
Okay, wait there for Ulrich and Odd,
and watch out for XANA’s monsters.
Well, are you ready?
Here we go.
Transfer Ulrich.
Transfer Odd.
Scanner Odd.
Scanner Ulrich.
Virtualization.
Odd! Ulrich!
There she is.
Good news.
XANA’s still not in control of the TV dish.
That gives us a little time.
I’ll try to find out which satellite
XANA might want to get his hands on,
but it won’t be easy.
No more phones,
no more school!
Okay, now let’s try the access code.
Access code accepted.
Yes!
Bingo!
Let’s see…U466.
Military satellite armed with…
a highly-destructive laser beam!
Where can that tower be?
One thing at a time, Odd.
First of all, I figured it out.
I know what XANA’s after.
He wants to gain control
of a highly-accurate
and destructive satellite.
If he does, he can destroy
whatever he wants.
The factory’s safe.
XANA wouldn’t fire at himself.
Right.
That’ll give us time to
take care of things on Lyoko.
Sounds good.
But if XANA decides
to destroy the school…
Remember, YumI’s there,
so that’s for sure what he’s gonna do.
We have to warn her.
But without a mobile…
No more phones,
no more school!
No more phones, no more--
I demand that you stop
this absurd strike now!
Kiwi?
Yumi, what is going on?
Well, I--
This is inadmissible!
To my office! Immediately!
Did you see that?
We have to save her
from the dictator!
Free Yumi!
Liberty for Yumi!
Free Yumi! Free Yumi!
According to the holomap,
the tower is just across the bridge.
But be careful.
It’s probably guarded by those…
By the waspsters.
Thanks, we’ve noticed.
Remember, the poison they’re carrying
will kill your life points, so watch out.
What are they waiting for?
They must just want to hold you there
until XANA’s able to control the satellite.
You’ve got to get past them.
Laser arrow!
No, Aelita! Watch out!
Aelita, don’t take any chances.
Leave that to Odd and Ulrich.
Yumi, I don’t understand! What’s going on?
A strike, a dog…
You’re usually so sensible, too.
Yumi, will you listen to me?
I’m sorry, sir, but I
have to leave right away.
You too, as a matter of fact!
Everyone around here has to leave!
We have no choice.
One of you has to make the sacrifice.
Listen, I’ll attract their attention
so you can get through.
Here I go.
Odd, wait!
Take that!
He’s nuts.
Okay, let’s go.
Yeah, take that!
Ow!
Odd, between the poison and the arrows
you’ve already lost seven life points!
You said no choice!
There, you horrible beast!
You’ve only got 20 life points left, Odd!
I’m sorry.
Oh, no. XANA’s taken over the satellite!
Hurry!
He let you go, Yumi?
I escaped when he wasn’t looking.
What?
Because our…
our demands are more important
than anything for me!
In fact, we should increase
the strength of our movement
and protest in town!
Everyone, into town!
We’ve got to get
all the schools on our side!
Okay!
Let’s go! Freedom for
all our schools! Come on!
No more phones,
no more school!
Wow, what an incredible
technological masterpiece.
Parameters locked in place. Target localized.
Already?
We were right.
The school’s in the satellite’s line of fire.
But…
High school students,
middle school students,
all for one and one for all!
Come on, come on, faster!
You will not leave the grounds.
You have no right!
What’s going on?
I thought the tower
was supposed to be here.
10 life points left.
Ulrich, it’s game over for me.
Oh, no.
Ulrich, Aelita,
the waspsters are after you!
The holomap doesn’t lie.
It’s got to be here somewhere.
Triplicate!
Go on, don’t worry about me.
I wonder how accurate
this satellite really is.
I don’t believe it.
Yumi’s in danger!
The laser’s aimed right at her!
You’re making a terrible mistake!
I beg of you, sir, we’ve all
got to get out of here!
I have had enough, Yumi.
I’m suspending you for a month.
You and your dog
are to leave this campus now.
As for the rest of you,
back to your classrooms.
This strike is over!
Sir, it’s a question of life and death!
Let us all leave, please!
Hey, aren’t you being
a little dramatic, Yumi?
Yumi!
To the factory! Hurry!
It’s you the satellite’s after!
Laser flight path locked.
Satellite ready to fire.
It’s all over. XANA’s gonna fire!
Come on, we have to reach the factory.
It’s the only place that’s safe.
What in the world is happening?
Let’s get out of here now!
Aelita, have you found it yet?
Time’s running out!
I’m doing my best,
but nothing yet.
It’s pretty well hidden.
Ulrich, Aelita, answer me!
I’m here, Jeremie, but Ulrich’s out cold.
I still haven’t found the tower.
Ulrich, can you hear me?
Yes, Aelita.
Have you found the tower yet?
I think I have.
Okay, go.
Jeremie, I found it!
To the boiler room. Ready?
It’s now or never. Let’s go.
Yumi!
No!
Return to the past now.
Invitations to a party?
Not really.
What is this thing?
“Official school policy
reminder to all students.
“All mobile phones not turned off
before entering the classroom
“will be immediately confiscated?”
That’s incredible.
Talk about teacher’s pets!
Anyway, I’d like to see someone
try to confiscate my mobile.
You’re so brazen!
(LAUGHTER)
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED BY
REDDIT.COM/R/CODELYOKO